bizzdirectory.com 2012-11-08

# Bizz Directory - Business Web Directory - Privacy Policy and Terms

## Privacy Policy and Terms

We respect the privacy of all visitors to our website. We are committed to protecting the privacy of the users of its website and services. We want you to use and enjoy the website without having to reveal more information than necessary. 

You can access, browse our web site without disclosing your personal data. We do not collect any personal data from our visitors when they use our services.

Our Web server automatically receives anonymous "general usage data" which could include a record of which pages at our website visitors frequent the most. This information helps us determine which type of software and computing resources are most popular with our viewers and allows us to serve them better. Unless required by law, we will not share our users’ personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties. 

In order to serve advertisements to this site, third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" or web beacons on your browser. If we are utilizing an Advertising Network that sets cookies, we would not receive or collect any of the information. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

This website provides external links to other websites. We are not responsible and cannot control the content and security of other sites you visit once you leave our website.

We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. We will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home page. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit our site. For additional information or question, please contact us.

When you visit our web site to provide advertising services to third-party advertising companies use. The companies, this website and other websites from your visits to the (your name, address, e-mail address or phone number other than your) information capture products and services of interest to you advertising to show you can use.

**Third-Party Advertisers**

This application and to learn about the information used by these companies to block what options you want to know [ NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf) (PDF) documents, please see Appendix A. Language is subject to change at any time NAI'nın example, do not forget.   
****

**Google as the third-party vendors, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.**   
Google, by using the DART cookie to your users, your site and other sites on the Internet to deliver ads based on their visits Users visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy may prevent the use of the DART cookie. This web site, users are deemed to have accepted the above-mentioned conditions.

 _Last updated: 18 March 2011_
